<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>论文 on 飞璠博客</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 论文 on 飞璠博客</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 21:18:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>A_Second Order_Noise Shaping_SAR_ADC_With_Passive_Integrator_and_Tri Level_Voting</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/a_second-order_noise-shaping_sar_adc_with_passive_integrator_and_tri-level_voting/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/a_second-order_noise-shaping_sar_adc_with_passive_integrator_and_tri-level_voting/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;词汇&#34;&gt;词汇&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ns&#34;&gt;NS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Noise-Shaping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sar&#34;&gt;SAR&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Successive Approximation Register&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;通过逐步逼近的方式获得模拟信号的数字表示&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ota-operational-transconductance-amplifier&#34;&gt;OTA (Operational Transconductance Amplifier)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;跨导运算放大器&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;总结&#34;&gt;总结&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paper describes a design of a second-order noise-shaping successive approximation register (SAR) analog-to-digital converter (ADC). The proposed ADC is designed to reduce the impact of noise and increase the dynamic range of the ADC. The design uses a passive integrator and tri-level voting techniques to achieve the desired performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The proposed ADC architecture consists of two main stages: a voltage-to-time converter and a SAR ADC. The voltage-to-time converter is used to convert the input voltage into a time interval. The time interval is then converted to a digital code using the SAR ADC. The proposed design uses a passive integrator to shape the quantization noise and reduce its impact on the signal. The tri-level voting technique is used to further reduce the impact of the quantization noise and improve the ADC&amp;rsquo;s linearity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paper presents detailed design and analysis of the proposed ADC, including the analysis of the noise and linearity performance of the ADC. The design is implemented in a 65nm CMOS process, and the experimental results show that the proposed ADC achieves a signal-to-noise and distortion ratio (SNDR) of 70dB and a spurious-free dynamic range (SFDR) of 85dB. The power consumption of the ADC is 1.56mW at a sampling rate of 10MS/s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, the paper presents a novel approach to design a second-order noise-shaping SAR ADC with improved noise and linearity performance. The proposed design can be used in a wide range of applications that require high-precision analog-to-digital conversion, such as wireless communication, sensor networks, and instrumentation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
