<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>英语 on 飞璠博客</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 英语 on 飞璠博客</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:33:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>单词(2023.2.25-3.4)</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023.2.25-3.4/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023.2.25-3.4/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023225&#34;&gt;2023.2.25&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, in the kingdom of Meganeton, there lived a brave and untamed prince. He was determined to ascertain the truth behind a long-standing dispute between his kingdom and its neighboring kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was a brilliant scientist and he decided to pursue the matter using the latest scientific methods. He built a solenoid, a device that uses an electric current to create a magnetic field, to measure the viability of the mass medium between the two kingdoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also used a logie, a device that measures the speed of sound, to measure the resonant frequency of the mass medium. He then used an insulator and coaxial cable to protect the device from interference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was intrigued when his experiment revealed that the mass medium was anisotropic, meaning it had different properties in different directions. He suspected that this was the source of the dispute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To further investigate, the prince used a retarder, a device that slows down the speed of sound, to see if the properties of the mass medium could be changed. He then used cellophane to cover the retarder and see if it changed the properties of the mass medium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was delighted to find that the cellophane had indeed changed the properties of the mass medium. He was finally able to ascertain the truth behind the long-standing dispute and bring peace between the two kingdoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023226&#34;&gt;2023.2.26&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time there lived a boorish prince who was always befuddling the courtiers with his austere attitude. He was so cajoling that no one could ever guess what he was thinking. He was known for his candor but his words were so sharp that they often left people exhausted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, the prince decided to test the courtiers by giving them a difficult problem. He asked them to solve a combinatorial problem that involved partitioning a set of bolts into pairwise disjoint sets with different alleles. The courtiers were taken aback by the problem and tried their best to solve it but to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince, who was already in a bad mood, became even more frustrated and ordered them to solve the problem using the binomial axiom and an exhaustive search. The courtiers were now completely befuddled and exhausted. They had no idea how to proceed and begged the prince for mercy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the prince was in no mood to show mercy and continued to insist that they solve the problem. After much cajoling, the courtiers finally managed to solve the problem and the prince was satisfied. However, their solution was not perfect and had a few defects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince, who was known for his abstinence, refused to accept the solution and demanded that they find a perfect solution. The courtiers, who were already exhausted, had no choice but to try again. After a long and tedious search, they finally managed to find a perfect solution and the prince was pleased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The courtiers had finally managed to solve the problem, much to their posterior!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
