<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>英语 on 飞璠博客</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 英语 on 飞璠博客</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 14:50:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Part Interview</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/part-interview/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 14:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/part-interview/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;自我介绍&#34;&gt;自我介绍&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;原则&#34;&gt;原则&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;专业化&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;突出&lt;strong&gt;学历和工作经验&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;突出&lt;strong&gt;成就&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;注重&lt;strong&gt;逻辑&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;优缺点-dos-and-donts&#34;&gt;优缺点 (Dos and Don&amp;rsquo;ts)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;dos&#34;&gt;Dos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您的技能和经验与职位相关的方面&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;您对公司和职位的了解，包括其文化和价值观。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;您的热情和动机，以及您为什么对这个职位感兴趣。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;与过去的职位和项目相关的成功故事和经验。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;关于您的教育和培训的信息。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;donts&#34;&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;ts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;不要提及个人信息，除非它们与职位相关&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;避免涉及敏感话题&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;不要谈论您过去的雇主或同事的负面评论&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;避免过多地提及您的薪资期望。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;不要出现过于自大或傲慢，也不要表现出过于谦虚&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;star-技巧&#34;&gt;STAR 技巧&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Situation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Task&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Action&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Results&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>单词(2023 3.13-3.19)</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023-3.13-3.19/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 12:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023-3.13-3.19/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--313&#34;&gt;2023  3.13&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a script sophomore, Alex was always looking for ways to improve his craft. He had spent countless hours studying the works of great writers and had even taken classes to hone his skills. So when he was approached by a film director to write the script for a new sci-fi movie, Alex was over the moon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie was about a team of scientists who had developed a new voltaic module that could harness the power of lightning. But when the module falls into the wrong hands, the team must race against time to stop it from being used as a weapon of mass destruction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex dove into the project with zeal, spending long hours at his desk crafting the perfect script. He carefully considered each character&amp;rsquo;s intonation, making sure their words conveyed just the right emotion. He wanted the dialogue to feel natural, but also to have a certain swing to it, like music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the deadline approached, Alex realized that something was missing. He wanted to add a ritual to the movie, something that would make it feel more authentic. He thought about it for a while, then hit upon an idea. He would introduce an artifact, something that had been used in the past to harness the power of lightning. It would be a barbed object, ancient and mysterious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But as Alex sat down to write the scene, he realized he had a problem. He had only a few hours to finish the script, and he had no idea what the artifact should look like. He panicked for a moment, then took a deep breath and decided to improvise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He closed his eyes and pictured the artifact in his mind, trying to conjure up an image that would be both menacing and powerful. Suddenly, he saw it: a gleaming, tarnished object, covered in intricate designs that seemed to pulse with energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a surge of inspiration, Alex began to write. The words flowed from his fingers like lightning, and he knew that he had created something special. He put the finishing touches on the script, then sent it off to the director with a sense of pride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he waited for the director&amp;rsquo;s response, Alex knew that something big was imminent. He had poured his heart and soul into the script, and he believed that it was something truly special. And when the director called him the next day to tell him that the script was perfect, Alex knew that he had found his calling. He was a writer, and nothing could tarnish that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--314&#34;&gt;2023  3.14&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, in a distant land, there lived a wise old man named Caius. He was renowned for his knowledge of the world and his ability to answer any question put before him. He spent his days in his study, surrounded by books and scrolls, delving deep into the mysteries of the universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caius was particularly interested in the concept of ontology - the study of what exists and how it exists. He was fascinated by the idea that everything in the world could be broken down into a set of fundamental building blocks, which he called &amp;ldquo;paradigms.&amp;rdquo; He spent countless hours pondering the nature of these paradigms and how they interacted with each other to form the world as we know it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, as he was studying the concept of entropy - the gradual decline into disorder - Caius stumbled upon a mythical tome that had been lost to the world for centuries. This tome contained knowledge that was said to be so powerful that it could conjure up the very forces of the universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excited by his discovery, Caius began to delve deeper into the pages of the tome. As he read, he discovered that the knowledge contained within was based on a set of principles that were not deterministic, but rather stochastic - meaning that they were subject to chance and probability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caius was at first skeptical of this new way of thinking, but as he continued to study the tome, he began to realize that it held the key to a new understanding of the world. He began to incorporate the principles of stochasticity into his own work on ontology, and soon found that it opened up a whole new realm of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using the knowledge he had gained from the mythical tome, Caius was able to conjure up new paradigms that had never been seen before. He began to understand that the world was not a static, unchanging entity, but rather a dynamic and ever-evolving one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Caius continued his work, he began to notice that the principles of ontology and stochasticity were inextricably linked. He realized that the very act of observing a system could change its fundamental nature, and that the way we perceive the world around us could shape its very existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And so, Caius spent the rest of his days studying the mysteries of the universe, always searching for new paradigms and new ways of understanding the world. He knew that the universe was a complex and ever-changing entity, but he also knew that with the right mindset and the right tools, anything was possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--315&#34;&gt;2023  3.15&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bell in the tailor shop rang as the door opened, announcing the arrival of a new customer. The tailor looked up from his workbench and saw a wretch of a man standing in the doorway, his clothes in tatters and his face gaunt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What can I do for you?&amp;rdquo; the tailor asked, trying not to show his revulsion at the man&amp;rsquo;s appearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need a suit,&amp;rdquo; the wretch said, his voice barely above a whisper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tailor sighed. He had seen many customers like this before, people who were down on their luck and had no money to spare. But he had a business to run, and he couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford to give away his services for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Very well,&amp;rdquo; he said, &amp;ldquo;but I must warn you that I cannot offer my usual quality of work for the price you are likely to pay.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I understand,&amp;rdquo; the wretch said, nodding his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tailor took the man&amp;rsquo;s measurements and gave him a price. It was lower than his usual rate, but still more than the wretch could afford. He hesitated for a moment, then asked if he could pay in installments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tailor agreed, but imposed a strict schedule of payments. He didn&amp;rsquo;t trust the wretch to keep his word, and he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be left with an unpaid bill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wretch left the shop, and the tailor returned to his work. He began to cut the cloth for the suit, using the same iterative process he always used, taking care to make every cut precise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he worked, he heard the sound of keyclicks from the typewriter in the office next door. His neighbor was a writer, and spent most of his days hunched over his keyboard, working on his latest novel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tailor shook his head, wondering how anyone could spend so much time on such a solitary pursuit. He preferred the company of his customers, even the wretches who came in from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Days turned into weeks, and the wretch returned to the shop every few days to make his payments. He was always polite and respectful, but the tailor sensed that he was hiding something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, the tailor asked him what had brought him to such a low state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I lost everything,&amp;rdquo; the wretch said, his eyes downcast. &amp;ldquo;My job, my family, my home. I have nothing left.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tailor felt a pang of sympathy for the man. He had been fortunate in his life, never having to worry about where his next meal would come from or whether he would have a roof over his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He resolved to do his best for the wretch, to make him a suit that would give him the confidence he needed to start over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weeks turned into months, and the suit began to take shape. The tailor worked tirelessly, taking extra care with every stitch and seam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, the day came when the suit was ready. The wretch came to the shop to try it on, and the tailor was pleased to see that it fit him perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Thank you,&amp;rdquo; the wretch said, his eyes shining with gratitude. &amp;ldquo;This is more than I ever expected.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tailor smiled, feeling a sense of pride in his work. He had done his best for the wretch, and he knew that the suit would give him the confidence he needed to start over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--316&#34;&gt;2023  3.16&lt;/h1&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>CS4 CL Portfolio Profile</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/cs4-cl-portfolio-profile/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 14:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/cs4-cl-portfolio-profile/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;cover-letterconnect-the-dots&#34;&gt;Cover Letter——&amp;ldquo;Connect the dots&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cv&#34;&gt;CV&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just an outline of your Professional History.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;特点&#34;&gt;特点&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professional Introduction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sales Pitch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;structure--a-possible-one&#34;&gt;Structure —— A Possible One&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;开头&#34;&gt;开头&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姓名 + 自己的居住地&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;日期&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;公司名称 + 公司地址&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;正文&#34;&gt;正文&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt; did I find the ad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brief &lt;strong&gt;Self-Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why&lt;/strong&gt; do I &lt;strong&gt;write&lt;/strong&gt; this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why&lt;/strong&gt; do I &lt;strong&gt;fit&lt;/strong&gt; for this job&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highlight my &lt;strong&gt;Exp. and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A strong finish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;personal-profiles--portfolio-development&#34;&gt;Personal Profiles &amp;amp; Portfolio Development&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cv-career-objective&#34;&gt;CV Career Objective&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;结构&#34;&gt;结构&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;是谁+会啥+想干啥&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;要求&#34;&gt;要求&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;明确&lt;strong&gt;职业目标&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;seeking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;keen to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;wishing to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;强调&lt;strong&gt;技能、经验&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;with &amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注重个人特点&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简洁&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;不要&lt;strong&gt;人称&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;video-profiles&#34;&gt;Video Profiles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;内容&#34;&gt;内容&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;要求-1&#34;&gt;要求&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;调好&lt;strong&gt;相机视角&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;保证&lt;strong&gt;声音清晰&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;和谐的&lt;strong&gt;背景&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;打好&lt;strong&gt;灯光&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;不要有&lt;strong&gt;背稿痕迹&lt;/strong&gt;,也&lt;strong&gt;不要临场发挥&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;眼神&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>单词(2023 3.5-3.12)</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023-3.5-3.12/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023-3.5-3.12/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--35&#34;&gt;2023  3.5&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time in a laboratory far away, there was a scientist who worked with materials such as arsenide, gallium, and germanium. One day, while conducting an experiment on diffusion and drift, he decided to dope the materials to create an intrinsic semiconductor. However, something went wrong and the material became devoid of any useful properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frustrated, the scientist walked down the long corridor of the laboratory when suddenly he felt a surge of inspiration. He realized that he could still use the material for something else. Excitedly, he ran back to his lab and began to tamper with his experiment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, his hard work paid off and he was able to create something new and useful from what had seemed like a failure. And so, our scientist learned that sometimes it takes a little bit of creativity and determination to turn things around&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--37&#34;&gt;2023  3.7&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a seasoned detective, John knew that the key to any successful investigation was to proceed with caution. He carefully studied the case files, examining the evidence and piecing together the clues. The case was complex and he needed to be on his toes at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, as he was going through the suspect&amp;rsquo;s profile, he noticed something odd. The man had a history of drug abuse and his last arrest was for possession of dope. John knew that this was a potential lead that could help him crack the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He decided to resume his investigation, delving deeper into the suspect&amp;rsquo;s drug connections. He started tracking down the people the suspect had been associating with and soon enough, he discovered a cascade of drug-related crimes that were linked to the suspect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail led John to a notorious drug lord who was known for supplying drugs to high-profile clients. This was a breakthrough for John, but he knew that he had to be careful. The drug lord had a reputation for being ruthless and he would not hesitate to eliminate anyone who got in his way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John gathered his team and made a plan to arrest the drug lord and his associates. The operation was a success and they managed to seize a large quantity of drugs that were being circulated in the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he sat down to write his report, John realized that this case had been one of the toughest he had ever worked on. But the feeling of satisfaction he got from cracking it was unparalleled. He knew that the people of the city were safer now that the drug lord was behind bars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--38&#34;&gt;2023  3.8&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time in a faraway land, there was a lowly caterpillar who lived in the fields. Despite his lowliness, he had big dreams and always prioritized his goals. One day he came up with a scheme to obviate the need for crawling on the ground. He would become a hybrid creature that could fly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He began to formulate a plan and devised a way to streamline his transformation. With the help of his friends, he was able to facilitate the process and supervise every step of the way. They even managed to overhaul his entire body structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he emerged from his cocoon, he was vivid with phosphorous colors. His wings were intact and free from any impurities such as boron or other depletion elements. He even had a warranty for his covalent bonds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a salutation and sales pitch, he took off into the sky. He flew over fields of crops and used his new comparator vision to see the world in a whole new way. The diffusion of air over his wings made him feel alive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he reached the penultimate point of his journey, he realized that all along he had been genuine in his desire to change. And with that thought in mind, he soared higher than ever before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--39&#34;&gt;2023  3.9&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was a brilliant engineer named Sam. Sam had always been fascinated by the concept of electricity and spent most of his days tinkering with circuits and devices in his workshop. One day, he decided to design a new kind of transistor that would revolutionize the electronics industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam knew that in order to create this new transistor, he would need to understand the properties of a certain phenomenon called the Zener avalanche effect. This effect occurs when a voltage across a semiconductor junction exceeds a certain threshold, causing a rapid increase in current that can damage the device. Sam spent months studying the Zener effect, poring over datasheets and testing different materials in his lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, Sam discovered a way to use the Zener effect to create a new type of transistor that could operate at much higher frequencies than existing models. He called this device the Zener transistor, and it quickly became the talk of the electronics world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Sam&amp;rsquo;s success was short-lived. After a few months of production, he began to notice that the Zener transistors were reaching a point of saturation, where they could no longer handle any more current. This was a problem that had plagued transistor designers for years, and it threatened to undermine Sam&amp;rsquo;s breakthrough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Determined to find a solution, Sam once again turned to his trusty workshop. He experimented with different materials, altered the profile of the transistor, and even changed the pitch of the semiconductor layers. Finally, after months of trial and error, Sam discovered a way to increase the saturation point of the Zener transistor, making it a viable option for high-power applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam&amp;rsquo;s Zener transistor became a game-changer in the electronics industry, paving the way for faster, more efficient devices. And to this day, engineers around the world continue to build upon Sam&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking work, pushing the limits of what is possible in the field of electronics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--310&#34;&gt;2023  3.10&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the small town of Cedarwood, a groundbreaking new technology was about to be unveiled. The local research team had been tinkering with an actuator that could control the throughput of a pore in a bidirectional manner, opening up exciting new possibilities for the medical and manufacturing industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they prepared for the big reveal, one of the researchers noticed some crosstalk in the device&amp;rsquo;s communications system. They quickly discovered that a residue from a wrapper used in an earlier experiment was causing the issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team worked tirelessly to fix the problem, but the deadline was looming, and they still couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the actuator to work properly. As they frantically tried to find a solution, they were struck by a sudden realization: the actuator was asynchronous, meaning it didn&amp;rsquo;t need to be perfectly in sync to function correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With renewed hope, the team quickly made the necessary adjustments, and the actuator came to life. The crowd at the unveiling was amazed as the device effortlessly controlled the pore&amp;rsquo;s throughput, opening up a whole new world of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, little did they know that the actuator&amp;rsquo;s success would soon be overshadowed by a deadly plague that would sweep across the town. As the situation grew more dire, the researchers worked tirelessly to find a solution, and they soon discovered that the same actuator that had once brought so much hope could be used to combat the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using the bidirectional control, they were able to deliver a powerful medication directly to the affected cells, effectively stopping the plague in its tracks. As the town began to recover, the once-misunderstood actuator became a symbol of hope and resilience, proving that even the smallest advancements can make a huge impact on the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--311&#34;&gt;2023  3.11&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, in a world far different from ours, there existed a society where communication was everything. People communicated with each other using a strange language that was composed of &amp;ldquo;bits&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Baud&amp;rdquo; that were rendered into &amp;ldquo;full-duplex&amp;rdquo; mode to ensure that there were no communication gaps. This was essential for the functioning of the society because it had a strict hierarchy that was constituted of different levels of power and influence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the top of this hierarchy were the &amp;ldquo;Renderers,&amp;rdquo; who were responsible for creating and customizing the communication channels that people used. They had the power to acknowledge or reject the requests of the people below them and could control the granularity of the communication channels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, a young boy named Cookie realized that he was stuck in an &amp;ldquo;idle&amp;rdquo; state, where he couldn&amp;rsquo;t communicate with anyone else in the society. He tried to send messages, but they were not acknowledged by the Renderers, and he couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Determined to find a solution, Cookie went on a quest to learn more about the communication channels and how they worked. He discovered that the Renderers were so focused on their own power and influence that they had forgotten about the needs of the people below them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cookie decided to take matters into his own hands and learned how to customize his communication channels to suit his needs. He found a way to bypass the hierarchy and communicate with other people directly, using a conjunction of bits and Baud that he had never used before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly but surely, other people in the society started to follow Cookie&amp;rsquo;s lead, and they too began to customize their communication channels. The hierarchy started to crumble, and people began to communicate with each other on an equal footing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, Cookie became a hero and was acknowledged by everyone in the society for his courage and ingenuity. He had shown that even the smallest bits of communication could have a significant impact and that sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to break free from the confines of the hierarchy to achieve true freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--312&#34;&gt;2023  3.12&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, in a world far beyond our own, there was a small village called Lagbar. This village was known for its vast array of artefacts that could be found throughout the town, each with its own unique history and story. Many travellers would come from far and wide to see these artefacts, but little did they know that there was one in particular that held a dark secret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This artefact was a small, barbed bucket that had been passed down through generations of the village&amp;rsquo;s butlers. It was said that this bucket had been used in a horrific ritual many years ago, and the butlers had kept it hidden away ever since. However, with the rise of employability and the need for tourism in the village, it was decided that the artefact would be put on display for all to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This decision was met with mixed reactions from the villagers. Some believed that it would bring in more tourists and therefore increase their income, while others deprecate the idea, fearing that the dark history behind the bucket would tarnish the village&amp;rsquo;s reputation. After much discussion, a consensus was reached, and the bucket was put on display.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, things took a turn for the worse when a group of teenagers visiting the village decided to play a game of Fortnite in the town square. Little did they know that the bucket&amp;rsquo;s dark energy had somehow made its way into the game, causing a stochastic batch of events to occur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, the game became multifaceted, with players speaking in different languages and battling against various mythical creatures. It soon became apparent that the bucket was draining the valence from the game, causing it to become more and more dangerous with each passing moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Desperate to fix the situation, the village elders decided to hone their skills and liaise with the teenagers in order to find a way to stop the game. After much trial and error, they discovered that the only way to break the curse was to destroy the bucket once and for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With much hesitation, the elders destroyed the cursed artefact, and the game returned to normal. The villagers were relieved, but they knew that they had to be more careful with the artefacts they put on display in the future. For they knew that in a world of magic and mystery, even the smallest artefact could have a great power.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>CS2-3 毕业生 简历 实习</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/cs2-3-%E6%AF%95%E4%B8%9A%E7%94%9F-%E7%AE%80%E5%8E%86-%E5%AE%9E%E4%B9%A0/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/cs2-3-%E6%AF%95%E4%B8%9A%E7%94%9F-%E7%AE%80%E5%8E%86-%E5%AE%9E%E4%B9%A0/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;skills-for-career-success&#34;&gt;Skills for Career Success&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;transferrable-skills&#34;&gt;transferrable skills&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem-solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adaptability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-motivation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teamwork&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical thinking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;21th-century-skills&#34;&gt;21th Century Skills&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical thinking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adaptability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creativity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital literacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Emotional intelligence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultural awareness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;graduate-attributes-ga&#34;&gt;Graduate Attributes (GA)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Graduate Attributes are the skills, knowledge, values and attributes that students are expected to acquire during their studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;types&#34;&gt;Types&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Academic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Transferable&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;internship-and-work-placement&#34;&gt;Internship and Work Placement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;internship&#34;&gt;Internship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An internship is a form of experiential learning that provides students and recent graduates with the opportunity to gain hands-on work experience in a professional setting. Internships can be paid or unpaid, and can last anywhere from a few weeks to a year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;work-placement&#34;&gt;Work Placement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Work placement is a type of job experience that allows students to gain practical experience in a professional working environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;difference&#34;&gt;Difference&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WP is a part of the degree(course)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finish WP earns academic credits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;jobs-and-cvs&#34;&gt;Jobs and CVs&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A curriculum vitae (CV) is a document that summarizes your academic and professional achievements, skills and experiences. A CV is different from a resume, which is typically shorter and more focused on specific skills and accomplishments relevant to a particular job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-to-include-in-a-cv&#34;&gt;What to Include in a CV&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact information: Include your full name, address, phone number and email address. You can also add other relevant information such as your LinkedIn profile or personal website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Profile&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professional experience: Include the organization where you worked, the job title, the dates you were employed and a summary of your experience and achievements. Use bullet points to highlight your main responsibilities and accomplishments. Use action verbs and quantify your results whenever possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Academic history: List all schooling from high school through postdoctoral (if applicable). Include the title of the degree you earned, the year you graduated and the name of the school. You can also mention any honors, awards or scholarships you received.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skills: List any relevant skills that you have developed or demonstrated in your academic or professional career. These can include hard skills (such as languages, software or technical skills) or soft skills (such as communication, teamwork or leadership skills). You can also mention any certifications or licenses you have obtained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Publications: If you have published any papers, books, chapters or articles in academic journals or other outlets, list them here. Include the title of the publication, the name of the journal or publisher, the date of publication and any co-authors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Awards and honors: If you have received any recognition for your academic or professional work, such as prizes, grants, fellowships or scholarships, list them here. Include the name of the awarding institution or organization, the date of receipt and a brief description of what it was for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;References: If requested by the employer or institution you are applying to, provide contact details of two or three people who can vouch for your qualifications and performance. These can be former professors,
supervisors
or colleagues who know you well. Include their name,
title
and affiliation,
phone number
and email address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-format-your-cv&#34;&gt;How to Format Your CV&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no one right way to format your CV,
but there are some general guidelines
to follow:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use a clear
and professional font
such as Arial,
Times New Roman
or Calibri.
The font size should be between 10
and 12 points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use consistent formatting throughout your CV,
such as bolding
or italicizing headings,
using bullet points
or numbers for lists,
and aligning text
to the left margin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use white space
to separate different sections
and make your CV easy to read.
Avoid using too many colors,
graphics
or fancy fonts that may distract from your content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep your CV concise
and relevant.
Ideally,
it should be &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no longer than two pages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;,
unless you have extensive publications
or experience that require more space.
Focus on &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;highlighting your most important achievements
and skills that match the position you are applying for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proofread your CV carefully before sending it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;power-verb&#34;&gt;Power Verb&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition-1&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Verbs that convey a stronger sense of action and meaning when describing a behavior or action. These verbs often make sentences more *&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;vivid, forceful, and expressive&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;function&#34;&gt;Function&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using power verbs can enhance your ability to communicate, making your language more precise and specific.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;types-1&#34;&gt;Types&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;leadership-skills&#34;&gt;Leadership skills&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;articulated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;communicated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;conveyed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;delivered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;explained&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;facilitated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;influenced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;negotiated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;persuaded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboration:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;aligned&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;collaborated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;coordinated,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;engaged&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;fostered&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;partnered&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;supported&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;united&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;conceived,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;created&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;designed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;developed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;discovered&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;implemented&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;innovated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;launched&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;pioneered&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;analyzed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;devised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;established&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;formulated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;led&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;orchestrated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;planne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;strategized&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;achieved&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;completed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;delivered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;executed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;managed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;oversaw&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;produced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;使用方法&#34;&gt;使用方法&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use specific and relevant power verbs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use varied and diverse power verbs.
Avoid using the same verb over and over again
Instead use varied and diverse verbs that show different aspects of your leadership skills
For example instead of saying &amp;ldquo;I managed several projects&amp;rdquo;
say &amp;ldquo;I managed several projects
coordinated with cross-functional teams
and delivered high-quality results on time&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use action-oriented and positive power verbs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avoid using passive or negative verbs like &amp;ldquo;was&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;had&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;failed&amp;rdquo;
Instead use action-oriented
and positive verbs that show your initiative
and achievements For example instead of saying &amp;ldquo;I was responsible for a budget&amp;rdquo;
say &amp;ldquo;I administered a budget of $1 million
and reduced costs by 15%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://downeyflyfan.com/p/cs2-3-%E6%AF%95%E4%B8%9A%E7%94%9F-%E7%AE%80%E5%8E%86-%E5%AE%9E%E4%B9%A0/1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1209&#34;
	height=&#34;639&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://downeyflyfan.com/p/cs2-3-%E6%AF%95%E4%B8%9A%E7%94%9F-%E7%AE%80%E5%8E%86-%E5%AE%9E%E4%B9%A0/1_huf0bbc6866474b303ba5b15fa04c3b394_363624_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://downeyflyfan.com/p/cs2-3-%E6%AF%95%E4%B8%9A%E7%94%9F-%E7%AE%80%E5%8E%86-%E5%AE%9E%E4%B9%A0/1_huf0bbc6866474b303ba5b15fa04c3b394_363624_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;189&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;454px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>写作</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;技巧&#34;&gt;技巧&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;连接词&#34;&gt;连接词&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;开头&#34;&gt;开头&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To begin with&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;中间顺承&#34;&gt;中间(顺承)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In addition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Furthermore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Besides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;hellip; is also &amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moreover&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;中间转折&#34;&gt;中间(转折)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;but&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;However&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;still&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;中间因果&#34;&gt;中间(因果)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The aim was to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a result&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In this way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;引用&#34;&gt;引用&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research conducted by &amp;hellip; states/discovers that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was found that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;就而言&#34;&gt;就&amp;hellip;而言&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In terms of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When it comes to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With regard to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In respect of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With reference to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In relation to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;结束语&#34;&gt;结束语&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generally(Speaking)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All in all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;形容词&#34;&gt;形容词&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;好与坏&#34;&gt;好与坏&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;好&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;positive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;useful characteristic of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;坏&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;disadvantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;negative (aspect)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;drawback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flaw&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;多&#34;&gt;多&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;quite a lot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a large quantity (number) of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;numerous&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;countless&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;重要&#34;&gt;重要&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vital&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;significant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;important&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;crucial&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;essential&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;几乎-大概&#34;&gt;几乎 大概&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;nearly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;almost&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;nearly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;about&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;around&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;roughly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;approximately&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;原因与结果&#34;&gt;原因与结果&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;原因&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Result from&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On account of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;owing to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;结果&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;result in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;consequently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;attribute to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lead to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bring about&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;动词&#34;&gt;动词&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;发光&#34;&gt;发光&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;illuminate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;glow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lighten&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;摔-倒-掉&#34;&gt;摔 倒 掉&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;fall(down/into/to)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;drop&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;能够-做得好&#34;&gt;能够 做得好&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;could/can&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be able to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;is capable to/of&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;do well in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be good at&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;增和降&#34;&gt;增和降&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;增&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;increase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ascent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lift&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;uprise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;soar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;降&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;decrease&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;drop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;decline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lessen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;diminish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;reduce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;损害&#34;&gt;损害&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;destory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hurt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ruin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;break&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;spoil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;连词&#34;&gt;连词&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;通过&#34;&gt;通过&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;through&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;via&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;by&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;总结&#34;&gt;总结&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;不用序数词&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;连接词尽量不在句首&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第一条不用&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;，用&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后一条写&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In addition to&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;literature-review&#34;&gt;Literature Review&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;定义&#34;&gt;定义&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A published collection of written knowledge on or related to a particular subject.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;分类&#34;&gt;分类&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholarly Articles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reports&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;要求&#34;&gt;要求&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Existing Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; in the literature&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where do you fit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>单词(2023 2.25-3.3)</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023-2.25-3.3/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023-2.25-3.3/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--225&#34;&gt;2023  2.25&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, in the kingdom of Meganeton, there lived a brave and untamed prince. He was determined to ascertain the truth behind a long-standing dispute between his kingdom and its neighboring kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was a brilliant scientist and he decided to pursue the matter using the latest scientific methods. He built a solenoid, a device that uses an electric current to create a magnetic field, to measure the viability of the mass medium between the two kingdoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also used a logie, a device that measures the speed of sound, to measure the resonant frequency of the mass medium. He then used an insulator and coaxial cable to protect the device from interference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was intrigued when his experiment revealed that the mass medium was anisotropic, meaning it had different properties in different directions. He suspected that this was the source of the dispute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To further investigate, the prince used a retarder, a device that slows down the speed of sound, to see if the properties of the mass medium could be changed. He then used cellophane to cover the retarder and see if it changed the properties of the mass medium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was delighted to find that the cellophane had indeed changed the properties of the mass medium. He was finally able to ascertain the truth behind the long-standing dispute and bring peace between the two kingdoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--226&#34;&gt;2023  2.26&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time there lived a boorish prince who was always befuddling the courtiers with his austere attitude. He was so cajoling that no one could ever guess what he was thinking. He was known for his candor but his words were so sharp that they often left people exhausted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, the prince decided to test the courtiers by giving them a difficult problem. He asked them to solve a combinatorial problem that involved partitioning a set of bolts into pairwise disjoint sets with different alleles. The courtiers were taken aback by the problem and tried their best to solve it but to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince, who was already in a bad mood, became even more frustrated and ordered them to solve the problem using the binomial axiom and an exhaustive search. The courtiers were now completely befuddled and exhausted. They had no idea how to proceed and begged the prince for mercy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the prince was in no mood to show mercy and continued to insist that they solve the problem. After much cajoling, the courtiers finally managed to solve the problem and the prince was satisfied. However, their solution was not perfect and had a few defects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince, who was known for his abstinence, refused to accept the solution and demanded that they find a perfect solution. The courtiers, who were already exhausted, had no choice but to try again. After a long and tedious search, they finally managed to find a perfect solution and the prince was pleased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The courtiers had finally managed to solve the problem, much to their posterior!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--227&#34;&gt;2023  2.27&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was a philanthropist named Mr. Smith who was also a trendsetter in the world of finance. He had a vast portfolio of investments, and he was always looking for new ways to maximize his returns. One day, he came across a mathematical concept known as bivariate quantile regression, which he found very intuitive and fascinating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he studied this concept further, he realized that it could be used to analyze the progression of consecutive data points in his investments. He hired a team of mathematicians to help him develop a model that would allow him to identify trends and patterns in his portfolio using bivariate quantile regression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To his delight, he discovered that the model was also useful in the field of factorization. He found that he could use it to break down complex data sets into simpler components, which he could then analyze more easily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Mr. Smith&amp;rsquo;s interest in this new mathematical tool soon drew the attention of others in the finance industry. His competitors began to use similar models to analyze their own portfolios, and soon, the concept of bivariate quantile regression became widely known and used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the popularity of this mathematical tool grew, a corollary emerged – a new trend in the world of finance that emphasized the importance of understanding and analyzing data through mathematical models. Mr. Smith was proud to have been a part of this trendsetting movement, but he also felt a vague sense of unease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He realized that the unintended consequence of this movement was that it made the world of finance more decadent and exclusive. The hobo on the street had no access to these sophisticated mathematical tools, and he was left behind as the wealthy got even richer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Smith struggled with this ethical dilemma, but he ultimately decided to continue using bivariate quantile regression in his work. He knew that the linearity and closure of mathematical models could never fully capture the complexity of human life, but he hoped that he could use this tool to make a positive impact on the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he continued to use bivariate quantile regression in his work, Mr. Smith also became more involved in philanthropy. He used his wealth to support organizations that helped those who were less fortunate, hoping to balance out the unintended consequences of his work in finance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, Mr. Smith found solace in the fact that he was using his knowledge and resources to do good in the world, even if his work in finance had unintended consequences. He knew that there was no easy answer to the ethical questions that his work raised, but he hoped that he could continue to make a positive impact in his own small way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--228&#34;&gt;2023  2.28&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a statistician, Mary was accustomed to dealing with numbers and data. She had a mind that was always curious about patterns and trends, and she loved nothing more than to crunch the numbers and find correlations that others might have missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Mary had a dilemma on her hands. Her favorite appliance, a halogen lamp that she had been using for years, had finally given up the ghost. She had tried to replace the bulb, but the tungsten filament inside had expired, and there was no way to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mary knew that she needed to find a new lamp, but she was concerned about the environmental impact of her choice. She wanted to lessen her carbon footprint, but she also needed a lamp that would provide the right level of light for her work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she researched her options, Mary discovered that there were many types of bulbs available, each with their own advantages and disadvantages. She learned about kerosene lamps, which were cheap and easy to use, but not very bright. She read about neon lights, which were colorful and eye-catching, but not suitable for her work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, Mary discovered a type of bulb called a halogen incandescent. This bulb had many of the same features as her old halogen lamp, but it was more energy-efficient and had a longer lifespan. She also learned about the interchangability of bulbs and how some had a transresistance, while others had a transconductance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this newfound knowledge, Mary decided to aggregate all the information she had learned and make a decision. She settled on a halogen incandescent bulb that would provide the light she needed, while also being more environmentally friendly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Mary set up her new lamp, she couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but feel a sense of satisfaction. She had tackled her dilemma, learned a great deal about bulbs, and made a decision that she felt good about. And as she turned on the lamp and watched the light cascade over her work, she knew that she had made the right choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--31&#34;&gt;2023  3.1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was a young woman named Amy who was highly literate and had a passion for language and reading. However, she struggled to find a satisfying job. She had worked as a job-hopper in many companies, but she persevered in her search for better opportunities while also working to improve her skills and attributes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During her job search, Amy continuously worked to improve her interpersonal skills, learning to articulate her thoughts clearly and confidently in interviews. Her hard work and determination eventually paid off when she landed a job at a publishing house that specialized in historical books. The job required editors to have a deep understanding of history and be proficient in language expression, which Amy possessed from her love of studying history and reading books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her new role, Amy was responsible for creating a reminiscent histogram of historical events that were then published in the form of books. She also had to work overtime to meet deadlines and received overtime pay for her efforts. Despite the pressure, Amy found solace in her passion for history and language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although she faced some challenges along the way, including saturation in the market and high competition for jobs, Amy remained focused on her goal. She persevered through the difficulties, using phonetic techniques to improve her speaking skills and eye drops to relieve the strain on her eyes from hours of reading and editing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Albeit the challenges, Amy&amp;rsquo;s hard work and dedication paid off, and she found success in her career as an editor, thanks to her exceptional literacy and interpersonal skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--32&#34;&gt;2023  3.2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was a young writer named Emily. She had just finished writing her first novel and was eager to get it published. She had researched various publishing houses and knew that her best chance of getting published was to attend a writer&amp;rsquo;s conference in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emily lived in a small town in the Midwest, so getting to New York City was not going to be easy. She started looking for transportation options and decided to take a round-trip train ride. The train would take her straight to the city and would give her plenty of time to work on her curriculum vitae and prepare for her internship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emily&amp;rsquo;s excitement was palpable as she boarded the train. She had never been to New York City before and was eager to explore the city that never sleeps. As the train chugged along, Emily could feel the traction of the locomotive as it pulled the freight behind it. She took a nibble of her sandwich and watched the scenery outside her window, feeling grateful for the opportunity to travel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the train approached New York City, Emily&amp;rsquo;s excitement turned to nerves. She knew that the publishing industry was highly competitive, and she wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if she was ready to tackle it. But she also knew that this was her chance to penetrate the industry and make a name for herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emily checked into her hotel and started working on her curriculum vitae. She knew that this was her chance to make a good impression on the publishing houses. She spent hours perfecting her CV, making sure that all of her skills and accomplishments were highlighted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next day, Emily attended the writer&amp;rsquo;s conference. She was amazed at the talent and skill of the other writers, but she also knew that she had something unique to offer. She attended workshops and panels, taking notes and learning as much as she could about the industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the conference, Emily decided to explore the city. She visited museums, art galleries, and parks, soaking in the culture and vibrancy of New York City. She even got to see the Statue of Liberty up close, marveling at its composite structure and the history it represented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Emily prepared to leave New York City, she knew that she had gained valuable experience and knowledge. She had not yet secured a publishing deal, but she felt that she had made progress in her pre-dependency. She knew that she still had a long way to go, but she felt a renewed sense of determination and focus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the train ride back home, Emily looked out the window and watched the scenery blur past her. She knew that her journey was just beginning and that there would be challenges ahead. But she also knew that she had the skills and knowledge to overcome them. With renewed focus and an asymptotic drive to succeed, Emily felt ready to override any obstacle that stood in her bearing towards achieving her dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023--33&#34;&gt;2023  3.3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The locomotive chugged along the tracks, carrying a ragtag group of rebels to their destination. They had been fighting against the oppressive regime for years, hoping to restore freedom and democracy to their land. They had faced many hardships and losses, but they never gave up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of them was Lila, a young woman who had joined the rebellion after her family was killed by the regime’s soldiers. She had a knack for hacking and sabotage, and she had been pivotal in many successful missions. She was also in charge of maintaining the locomotive, which was an old model that had been salvaged from a junkyard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She loved the locomotive, despite its flaws and degradation. It was like a friend to her, a loyal companion that always got them where they needed to go. She knew every inch of it, every wire and bolt and valve. She could fix anything that went wrong with it, using whatever tools and materials she could find.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was in the engine room now, checking on the status of the locomotive. She looked at the control panel, which showed various indicators and gauges. Everything seemed normal, except for one thing: the quadratic equation solver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The quadratic equation solver was a device that helped calculate the optimal speed and acceleration of the locomotive based on various factors such as terrain, weather and load. It was supposed to be unbiased and accurate, but Lila noticed that it was giving strange results lately. Sometimes it would suggest speeding up when they should slow down or vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lila suspected that someone had tampered with it or hacked into it somehow. She wondered if it was an enemy spy or a traitor among them. She decided to investigate further and find out who was behind this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She opened up the device’s casing and examined its circuitry. She saw something that made her gasp: a small chip attached to one of the wires. It looked like a transmitter or receiver of some kind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She realized that someone had planted this chip inside the device to manipulate its output remotely. Whoever did this could control the speed and direction of the locomotive without anyone noticing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lila felt a surge of anger and fear. Who would do such a thing? And why? What were they planning?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She quickly removed the chip from the wire and pocketed it. She then closed up the casing again and pretended nothing happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She decided to keep this discovery secret for now until she could figure out who was responsible for this sabotage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She left the engine room and headed back to her seat in one of the passenger cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As she walked through the corridor, she scanned the faces of her fellow rebels, looking for any signs of guilt or suspicion. But everyone seemed normal, engaged in their own conversations or activities. No one looked at her with anything other than respect or friendship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lila felt confused and frustrated. How could she find out who did this? And how could she prevent them from doing more harm?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She reached her seat and sat down next to her best friend, Remy. He smiled at her and asked how she was doing. Lila forced herself to smile back and said she was fine. But inside, she felt anything but fine. She felt like she was in danger, like everything she cared about was at stake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She looked out the window, hoping to find some comfort in the scenery outside. But all she saw was a blur of colors and shapes, a vacant landscape devoid of life or meaning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wondered if they would ever reach their destination, if they would ever see their dream come true, if they would ever be free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She wondered if anyone else knew about the chip in the quadratic equation solver,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and what they were going to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(End of Week II)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
