<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>英语 on 飞璠博客</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 英语 on 飞璠博客</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:33:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://downeyflyfan.com/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>单词(2023.2.25 3.4)</title>
        <link>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023.2.25-3.4/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://downeyflyfan.com/p/%E5%8D%95%E8%AF%8D2023.2.25-3.4/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;2023225&#34;&gt;2023.2.25&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, in the kingdom of Meganeton, there lived a brave and untamed prince. He was determined to ascertain the truth behind a long-standing dispute between his kingdom and its neighboring kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was a brilliant scientist and he decided to pursue the matter using the latest scientific methods. He built a solenoid, a device that uses an electric current to create a magnetic field, to measure the viability of the mass medium between the two kingdoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also used a logie, a device that measures the speed of sound, to measure the resonant frequency of the mass medium. He then used an insulator and coaxial cable to protect the device from interference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was intrigued when his experiment revealed that the mass medium was anisotropic, meaning it had different properties in different directions. He suspected that this was the source of the dispute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To further investigate, the prince used a retarder, a device that slows down the speed of sound, to see if the properties of the mass medium could be changed. He then used cellophane to cover the retarder and see if it changed the properties of the mass medium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince was delighted to find that the cellophane had indeed changed the properties of the mass medium. He was finally able to ascertain the truth behind the long-standing dispute and bring peace between the two kingdoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prince&amp;rsquo;s courage and intelligence were praised by all and he was remembered as a hero for generations to come.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
